{"questions":
			[
				{
					"question":"Which of the following is not a keyword in java?",
					"A":"static",
					"B":"Main",
					"C":"void",
					"D":"private",
					"answer":"B"
				},
				{
					"question":"What is the default value of String variable?",
					"A":".",
					"B":"a",
					"C":"null",
					"D":"not defined",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"What is instance variable?",
					"A":"Instance variables are static variables within a class but outside any method.",
					"B":"Instance variables are variables defined inside methods, constructors or blocks.",
					"C":"Instance variables are variables within a class but outside any method.",
					"D":"None of the above.",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"Static binding uses which information for binding?",
					"A":"type",
					"B":"object.",
					"C":"Both of the above.",
					"D":"None of the above.",
					"answer":""
				},
				{
					"question":"Which is the way in which a thread can enter the waiting state?",
					"A":"Invoke its sleep() method.",
					"B":"Invoke object's wait method.",
					"C":"Invoke its suspend() method.",
					"D":"All of the above.",
					"answer":"D"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
					"A":"Bytecode is executed by JVM",
					"B":"The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
					"C":"Use of exception handling",
					"D":"Dynamic binding between objects",
					"answer":"A"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following is not a Java features?",
					"A":"Dynamic",
					"B":"Architecture Neutral",
					"C":"Use of pointers",
					"D":"Object-oriented",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following is a valid declaration of a char?",
					"A":"char cc = 'itea';",
					"B":"char ch = 'utea';",
					"C":"char ca = 'tea';",
					"D":"char cr = u0223;",
					"answer":"B"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following is not a keyword in java?",
					"A":"static",
					"B":"Main",
					"C":"void",
					"D":"private",
					"answer":"B"
				},
				{
					"question":"What is the default value of String variable?",
					"A":".",
					"B":"a",
					"C":"null",
					"D":"not defined",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"What is instance variable?",
					"A":"Instance variables are static variables within a class but outside any method.",
					"B":"Instance variables are variables defined inside methods, constructors or blocks.",
					"C":"Instance variables are variables within a class but outside any method.",
					"D":"None of the above.",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"Static binding uses which information for binding?",
					"A":"type",
					"B":"object.",
					"C":"Both of the above.",
					"D":"None of the above.",
					"answer":""
				},
				{
					"question":"Which is the way in which a thread can enter the waiting state?",
					"A":"Invoke its sleep() method.",
					"B":"Invoke object's wait method.",
					"C":"Invoke its suspend() method.",
					"D":"All of the above.",
					"answer":"D"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
					"A":"Bytecode is executed by JVM",
					"B":"The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
					"C":"Use of exception handling",
					"D":"Dynamic binding between objects",
					"answer":"A"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following is not a Java features?",
					"A":"Dynamic",
					"B":"Architecture Neutral",
					"C":"Use of pointers",
					"D":"Object-oriented",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following is a valid declaration of a char?",
					"A":"char cc = 'itea';",
					"B":"char ch = 'utea';",
					"C":"char ca = 'tea';",
					"D":"char cr = u0223;",
					"answer":"B"
				},
				{
					"question":"Which of the following is not a keyword in java?",
					"A":"static",
					"B":"Main",
					"C":"void",
					"D":"private",
					"answer":"B"
				},
				{
					"question":"What is the default value of String variable?",
					"A":".",
					"B":"a",
					"C":"null",
					"D":"not defined",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"What is instance variable?",
					"A":"Instance variables are static variables within a class but outside any method.",
					"B":"Instance variables are variables defined inside methods, constructors or blocks.",
					"C":"Instance variables are variables within a class but outside any method.",
					"D":"None of the above.",
					"answer":"C"
				},
				{
					"question":"Static binding uses which information for binding?",
					"A":"type",
					"B":"object.",
					"C":"Both of the above.",
					"D":"None of the above.",
					"answer":""
				}

			]
	
}